[Music]
So no digital is the newest part of no.
It's where a lot of our acquisitions
over the last six years have ended up
with a specialism around the Microsoft
services particularly within ERP cloud
AI and security. Today we're up to 550
but with rapid growth plans over the
coming years. Being one of the biggest
practices in the UK comes with its
challenges. often enough we have a hell
of a lot of roles open at one time which
is more than just one person's job. Our
initial request to the BC talent team
was to hire around seven people. They
actually delivered a surplus of
candidates. So we had a a very difficult
decision to make in the end. The amount
of people that will apply for these
positions and these opportunities is
unprecedented and it enables no four to
pick the best of the crop if you like
and within 2 weeks we're able to have
prevetted individuals having interviews
and we move the program along. The best
thing about this it just takes out a lot
of the time to get people through and
then ultimately billable. So it
expedites that whole process. Other
programs we could get involved in are
more generic, which means that when
resources land with us, then we've still
got to focus on the business central
element of the skilling up, whereas this
program is right in the sweet spot for
where we're putting our chips
strategically. Um, so that people come
into our business a lot more enabled,
which allows that we can get them out on
projects, delivering benefits to clients
a lot quicker. Straight out of the
program, we do a little bit of training
them on things like our methodology and
our ways of working, but week two, week
three definitely they will be either
chargeable consultants or within our
support desk working alongside our
customers. We can trust that we give
them a requirement. They go out and
source and qualify the right caliber of
people based on a requirement and all we
have to do is interview and make a
decision on who to bring on board. They
handle everything else for us. The
caliber of candidates we've had has been
second to none. the speed in which they
have joined into our organization and
started adding value has been
record-breaking. It's a rich mature
program um and it's generating results
for organizations like us. If you have
any plan to grow and and diversify your
talent pool, this is the right way to go
about bringing people into your
organization.